<resources>
    <string name="about_expl">NBSProxy exists only to forward small
    binary messages via Narrow Band Sockets (called \"data sms\" in
    the Android world) on behalf of other applications you\'ve
    installed.\n\nBecause NBS is a low-level feature of the GSM cell
    phone infrastructure, they only work on GSM networks (i.e. pretty
    much every network in the world except the US carriers Verizon and
    Sprint.)</string>

    <string name="main_perms_expl">To function, NBSProxy requires
    permission to send and receive SMS messages. That\'s because in
    the Android world NBS messages are considered a type of SMS,
    though in fact they\'re completely orthogonal to the user-visible
    text messages you probably exchange with friends and
    family.</string>

    <string name="permissions2">When you tap the \"Grant Permissions\"
    button below you\'ll see up to two Android system dialogs
    prompting you to confirm. You\'ll be asked to confirm SMS messages
    and managing phone calls. I have no idea why Android requires the
    latter for sending NBS data, but it does.</string>

    <string name="have_perms">NBSProxy has already been granted the
    permissions it needs to function. You may never need to launch it
    again.</string>

    <string name="perms_button_label">Request Permissions</string>

    <string name="uninstall_button_label">Uninstall</string>
    <string name="exit_button_label">Done</string>

    <string name="settings_expl">The built-in Settings app is where
    you go to view or revoke permissions. (You can also uninstall
    using Settings, but the \"Uninstall\" button below works \"for all
    users\", which is probably what you want.)</string>

    <string name="settings_button_label">Launch Settings</string>

    <string name="delete_expl">If you\'re not on a GSM phone or if
    you\'re not comfortable granting the permissions NBSProxy needs,
    you might as well uninstall. No hard feelings :-)</string>

    <string name="test_button_label_fmt">Send test to: %s</string>

    <string name="tab_about_title">About</string>
    <string name="tab_perms_title">Permissions</string>
    <string name="tab_test_title">Test</string>

    <string name="test_expl">Use the button below to confirm that NBS
    works on your phone. It sends 32 random bytes to your phone number
    and verifies that they\'re received unchanged.\n\nYou\'ll see a
    notification when the message is received, including how long it
    took.</string>

    <string name="tab_stats_title">Statistics</string>

    <string name="test_result_fmt">Send-to-self test succeeded, taking %.2f seconds.</string>

    <string name="stats_button_refresh">Update</string>
</resources>
